priceshield.com 2007-09-11

# PriceShield.com - Privacy Statement

**PriceShield Privacy Policy**

**PriceShield is a division of SmartShopper Networks Ltd. ("PriceShield")**

At PriceShield, we're committed to your privacy.

 **Our Privacy Policy is simple. We do not collect any personal information about you or your shopping habits (unless you choose to register with us). The information you enter when you search for a product or service is used to automatically compare and find the best deals on the web.  We do  not trade, rent or sell personally identifiable information ("PII") with third parties for marketing or any other purposes.**

Learn more about safe surfing and online shopping from the [Federal Trade Commission](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/alerts/glblalrt.htm).

**What information do we collect?**

(a) Anonymous Aggregate Information

PriceShield collects and stores aggregated information about the web pages its users view and the data they enter in search engine search fields while using the PriceShield software (the "Service").  PriceShield uses this information to determine which alternative offers to display on your browser window pane.  

For every web page you view while using the Service, the PriceShield software transmits from your computer to the PriceShield server and stores the following information: your Internet Protocol (IP) Address; the Full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the web page you are visiting; general information about your browser and your computer's operating system; your PriceShield cookie number and the date and time the above information is logged.  We also collect and store the following PriceShield usage statistics: what is clicked on the browser window pane; the amount of time the Service is used during each session; which keyword searches are performed and what alternative results are received during any given session.

If you are only visiting our site ([www.priceshield.com](http://www.priceshield.com/)), we collect the following information: the URL of the web page from which you came; your IP Address; the date and time of each page you view; the name of and information about any advertisement that brought you to our web site; and computer and connection information.  If the URL of the page from which you came contains any PII about you, we will not attempt to determine your identity by analyzing the URL in any way.

(b) Personally Identifiable Information

Some of our services may ask that you register.  Registration is optional and you may choose to use the PriceShield program without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself.  If you choose to register, PriceShield asks you for some PII (for example your name, email address, and a city or an airport near you) in order to create an account. 

Any PII which is collected, as described above, is stored separately from the information about the web pages you view and the data you enter in search engine search fields and the two types of information are not correlated or linked. 

Except as provided above, we do not gather PII from you without your specific permission when you visit the PriceShield site and download the PriceShield software or use the Service. 

**Cookies**

Upon visiting [www.priceshield.com](http://www.priceshield.com/), a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser.  This cookie assigns your Web browser a unique series of numbers, letters, or characters that enables PriceShield's servers to recognize and identify your web browser when you are using the Service and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you.  The cookie improves the quality of our service by getting a better understanding of how people interact with us.  Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions.    

**Clear Gifs**

We and our third party advertising companies employ a software technology called clear gifs (sometimes called web beacons), that help inform us of what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier which are used to track the online movements of users.  Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

PriceShield analyzes its logs of usage paths and stored search terms collected from users to build anonymous web usage profiles.  However, PriceShield stores this information separately from PII, and PriceShield does not correlate or link a user's anonymous usage profile to any PII about the user.  PriceShield uses these anonymous web usage profiles and stored search terms to determine alternative offers to display.

PriceShield does not:

(a)    Associate or store non-personally identifiable web usage data or search information with any PII; 

(b)   Analyze such web usage data or search information to determine the identity of any PriceShield user; or

(c)    Use PII to determine which ads and alternative offers to display on your PriceShield browser window pane. 

**Do we share the information we collect?**

1.  PII - We only share personally identifiable information with third parties under the following circumstances: 

·        We may share PII with third parties if we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, respond to judicial or administrative legal process or enforce or apply the terms of our user agreement or privacy policy. 

In the event that PriceShield sells substantially all of its assets or is acquired, the Service and all information collected by the Service would be transferred to the acquiring party.  In any such transfer, however, such information would remain subject to any terms and conditions applicable to the Service at the time the information was collected, including the terms of this Privacy Policy and any amendment thereto

·        From time to time, we may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as technical support services.  To perform those functions, it may be necessary for them to obtain access to PriceShield's databases and servers, which may contain PII about users. They may not use such access or information for any purpose other than that for which such companies and individuals are retained.

2\. Anonymous Information - PriceShield works with third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site and use the Service, including the browser window pane. We may share anonymous web site usage information about the PriceShield Service, including the browser window pane, with such companies for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our web sites and the Service For these purposes, we and out third party advertising companies may note some of the pages you visit on our web sites, and while using the Service, trough the use of clear gifs.

**Children's privacy**

This website is directed towards and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older.  We will not approve applications of, or establish or maintain accounts for, any child whom we know to be under the age of 13.  We do not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.  If we nevertheless receive personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is, under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our systems. 

**Third party sites**

PriceShield, from time to time, may work with affiliates and/or sponsors to offer users the opportunity to register for services or subscribe to various newsletters or other information services.  While we try to link only to websites that we believe share our respect for privacy, please be aware that PriceShield is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites and we encourage you to read the privacy statements and terms of use of such other third parties before you provide personally identifiable information to them since their privacy policy and terms of use shall apply to such activity. 

**Tell a friend**

PriceShield allows you to send messages or share your shopping results with friends via email.  If you choose to send a message ("tell a friend" or "share results") by email from our site to your acquaintance(s), the message will be sent only once.  Furthermore, the email addresses you provide in the "tell a friend" or "share results" process is used only to fulfill your request.  PriceShield does not transmit these email addresses for marketing purposes (or any other purposes) to any third parties.

**Software updates**

The Software is designed to check for the availability of software updates to ensure that you enjoy the latest improvements to the Software.  When the Software checks for the availability of software updates, anonymous information about the Software version and installed components is sent to our web server.  The information is used to determine whether new free software is available for download and is not associated with your PII. 

**OPT-OUT / Choices/ Changes**

Our site provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. To remove your email from our mailing list, you can simply click the "remove me from list" link at the bottom of each newsletter we send to you, or follow the steps below:

1.      Open the Options page by clicking on the options button on the PriceShield browser window pane.

2.      Under the General Information section insert the email address with which you have registered to the list (this email address also appears at the bottom of each newsletter we send to you) 

3.      Uncheck the "Keep me updated" checkbox 

4.      Press the "Save Preferences" button to submit the change.

To temporarily snooze, permanently disable or set usage rules for certain parts of the PriceShield Service, go to the browser window page, click "Options" , and select your preferences.

This site gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided. You may add or modify the provided information by clicking the options button / link on the left pane or the website.

**Removal of the priceshield software**

If you are having technical or other difficulty with the PriceShield comparative shopping application, please contact our support team at [support@priceshield.com](mailto:support@priceshield.com). To remove the PriceShield comparative shopping application you will need to uninstall the software using Microsoft's Windows control panel add/remove software function.

**Information security**

PriceShield undertakes reasonable physical, electronic and procedural security measures in order to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  We restrict access to the database that contains PII to a limited number of employees who may access that information only for legitimate business or legal purposes.  Those employees are instructed and trained to maintain the database while safeguarding the privacy of users.  While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot absolutely guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

PriceShield is constantly evolving.  New features are continuously being added to the site and software.  With these improvements, our Privacy Policy may evolve.  If this should happen, we will inform you through our site's homepage and this Privacy Policy.  

**How to contact us about privacy**

**** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site and Service, or your dealings with this web site, you can email us at: [privacy@priceshield.com](mailto:privacy@priceshield.com)

**This privacy policy was last updated on March 16, 2005.**
